Class Action Park is a documentary film directed by Seth Porges.
Class Action Park explores the legend, legacy, and truth behind the 1980s water
park in Vernon, New Jersey that long ago entered the realm of myth.
Known for its dangerous, unsupervised rides and lack of regulation, guests of Action Park
expected to walk away with injuries and were lucky if they made it out alive.
Shirking the trappings of nostalgia, the film uses investigative journalism, original animations,
recordings, and interviews with the people who lived it to reveal the true story of Action Park.
Self, played by Chris Gethard.
Self, played by Jason Scott.
Self (archive footage), played by Jimmy Kimmel.
Self (archive footage), played by Johnny Knoxville.
Self, played by Alison Becker.
Narrator, played by John Hodgman.
Class Action Park is a 2020 documentary film about the American amusement park Action Park, which was located in Vernon Township, New Jersey and was
known for the popularity it had among locals, and is infamous for the poor safety record of the attractions located on its grounds.
The title is based on one of the popular nicknames by parkgoers,
alongside "Traction Park" and "Accident Park".
The film premiered virtually at the 2020 Florida Film
Festival and was released a week later on HBO Max.
It premiered on TNT on December 27, 2021.
The film explores themes of fraud, accidental death, amusement park, injury.